<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
	<info>
		<name>Occultist Spells</name>
		<update version="0.0.1">
			<file name="spells-occultist.xml" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/mol-tres/AURORAS/master/REDDIT_UA/KIBBLES_TASTY/occultist/spells-occultist.xml" />
		</update>
	</info>
	
	
	<element name="Alacrity" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_ALACRITY">
		<supports>Bard, Sorcerer, Wizard, Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Until the spell ends, your speed is doubled, you gain a +2 bonus to AC, you have advantage on Dexterity saving throws, and you gain an additional action. That action can be used only to take the Attack (one weapon attack only), Dash, Disengage, Hide, or Use an Object action.</p>
			<p class="indent">If you are under the effect of <i>haste</i>, you gain no benefit from this spell.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">2</set>
			<set name="school">Transmutation</set>
			<set name="time">1 bonus action</set>
			<set name="duration">1 Round</set>
			<set name="range">Self</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">the hand of a broken clock</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Animate Object" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_ANIMATE_OBJECT">
		<supports>Bard, Sorcerer, Wizard, Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You bring a small or smaller object to life. Its Constitution is 10 and its Intelligence and Wisdom are 3, and its Charisma is 1. Its speed is 30 feet; if the object lacks legs or other appendages it can use for locomotion, it instead has a flying speed of 30 feet and can hover. The object has the following stats: HP: 20, AC: 18, Str: 4, Dex: 18. The object has an attack modifier equal to your spell attack modifier. If the object is a weapon, it deals damage equal to the weapon's damage dice + your Wisdom modifier on hit dealing that weapons damage type, otherwise it deals 1d4 + your Wisdom modifier bludgeoning damage on hit.</p>
			<p class="indent">As a bonus action, you can mentally command the animated object as long as it is within 60 feet of you. You decide what action the creature will take and where it will move during its next turn, or you can issue a general command, such as to guard a particular chamber or corridor. If you issue no commands, the creature only defends itself against hostile creatures. Once given an order, the creature continues to follow it until its task is complete.</p>
			<p class="indent">If the object is securely attached to a surface or a larger object, such as a chain bolted to a wall, its speed is 0. It has blindsight with a radius of 30 feet and is blind beyond that distance. When the animated object drops to 0 hit points, it reverts to its original object form, and any remaining damage carries over to its original object form. </p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">2</set>
			<set name="school">Transmutation</set>
			<set name="time">1 bonus action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">false</set>
			<set name="materialComponent" />
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Animate Shadow" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_ANIMATE_SHADOW">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Targeting a creature you can see within range, you bring it's shadow to life under your control. If the creature has a CR of more than 3 or the creature has no shadow (either from the nature of the creature or from the lack of a light source to cast one) the spell fails.</p>
			<p class="indent">Otherwise a copy of the creature is created using its game statistics is created adjacent to the creature (on the side away from the brightest light near it). The shadow has no legendary actions, legendary resistance, and cannot cast spells. The shadow creature has hit points equal to half the target's hit point, and looks like mirrored version of the creature it was summoned from formed from inky black smoke. The creature is resistant to bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage from non-magical sources while in darkness. The creature is vulnerable to all damage while in bright light, and always vulnerable to fire, lightning, and radiant damage. If the shadow is killed, the target creature it was summoned from casts no shadows for the next 8 hours.</p>
			<p class="indent">The shadow acts immediately after the creature's turn, and without further direction it attempts to follow and takes the attack action against it was summoned from. As a reaction to the shadow starting it's turn, the caster can exert control over it and cause it to move and take its action as the caster directs. </p>
			<p class="indent"><b><i>At Higher Levels. </i></b>When you cast this spell using a 5th- or 6th-level spell slot, the maximum CR of the target increases to CR 4. When you cast it using a 7th- or 8th-level spell slot, the maximum CR of the target increases to CR 5. When you cast it using a spell slot of 9th level or higher, the maximum CR of the target increases to CR 6.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">3</set>
			<set name="school">Illusion</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 hour</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a smoke stained mirror</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Baba's Walking Hut" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_BABAS_WALKING_HUT">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You touch a hut, cabin, or other building no more than 15 feet by 15 feet by 10 feet. On completion of the spell, the building grows legs large enough to support it, as well as the structural integrity needed stand and move, and becomes a gargantuan creature. It has 250 hit points, an AC of 12, and a walking speed of 20 feet. If it drops to 0 hit points, the spell ends.</p>
			<p class="indent">On your turn, you can direct it to move (no action required) and it will continue to move as directed until you direct it to stop or reaches its destination. It can take no actions, but if it walks over a large or smaller creature, you can direct it to attempt to step on that creature, and that creature must succeed a Dexterity saving throw, or take 2d10 bludgeoning damage and be knocked prone.</p>
			<p class="indent">If you cast this spell on the same building every day for a year, the spell lasts until dispelled.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">6</set>
			<set name="school">Illusion</set>
			<set name="time">10 minutes</set>
			<set name="duration">24 hours</set>
			<set name="range">Touch</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a chicken leg</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Befuddling Curse" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_BEFUDDLING_CURSE">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You befuddle a creature's mind, swapping the position of two things it can see that are of the same size and category (for example, two medium creatures or two gargantuan buildings). The target creature must make a Wisdom saving throw. On failure, it is unaware the two things have been swapped.</p>
			<p class="indent">Each time the creature interacts with, attacks, or is attacked by a swapped targets, it can repeat its saving throw against the effect.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">1</set>
			<set name="school">Enchantment</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">something from the target creature (such as blood, hair, or scales) which the spell consumes</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Binding Curse" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_BINDING_CURSE">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You bind a creature to a point within 5 feet of them, causing a glowing chains of light to connect them to that point. For the duration of the spell, if the creature attempts to move away from that point, the must make a Wisdom saving throw, or be unable to move more than 5 feet away from from that point until the start of their next turn.</p>
			<p class="indent">If a creature starts its turn more than 10 feet from the binding point, they must make a Strength saving throw are dragged 5 feet toward the binding point.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">1</set>
			<set name="school">Enchantment</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">something from the target creature (such as blood, hair, or scales) which the spell consumes</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Boil Blood" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_BOIL_BLOOD">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Targeting a creature that has taken slashing or piercing damage in the last minute, make it's blood heat and boil. The target creature must make a Constitution saving throw. On failure, it's blood begins to heat. At the start of it's turn while effected, it takes 3d4 fire damage and is crippled with agony, all terrain is difficult terrain for it.</p>
			<p class="indent">At the end of each of its turns, the target can make another Constitution saving throw. On a success, the spell ends on the target.</p>
			<p class="indent"><b><i>At Higher Levels. </i></b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 2d4 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">2</set>
			<set name="school">Transmutation</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">false</set>
			<set name="materialComponent" />
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Burn" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_BURN">
		<supports>Druid, Sorcerer, Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You ignite a brilliant flame around your hand that sears anything you touch. Make a melee spell attack against the target. You have advantage if the target creature type is plant, or if it has a vulnerability to fire damage. On hit, the target takes 1d12 fire damage.</p>
			<p class="indent">The spell's damage increases by 1d12 when you reach 5th level (2d12), 11th level (3d12), and 17th level (4d12).</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">0</set>
			<set name="school">Transmutation</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Instantaneous</set>
			<set name="range">Touch</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">false</set>
			<set name="materialComponent" />
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Curse of Impotence" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_CURSE_OF_IMPOTENCE">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You curse a target creature, causing an overwhelming sense of powerlessness to wash over them. Any time the target creature attempts to attack, cast a spell that deals damage, or use an action that deals damage, it must make a Wisdom saving throw. On failure, they complete their action, but their action does no damage to any target.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">5</set>
			<set name="school">Enchantment</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">something from the target creature (such as blood, hair, or scales) which the spell consumes</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Crippling Agony" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_CRIPPLING_AGONY">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You can inflicted crippling agony on a foe. Choose one creature that you can see within range to make a Constitution saving throw. If the target fails, it becomes crippled with horrific pain. Whenever the creation moves more than half of it's movement speed or takes an action, the crippling pain causes it to take 1d6 necrotic damage.</p>
			<p class="indent">It can repeat the saving throw at the end At the end of each of its turns, the target can make a Constitution saving throw. On a success, the spell ends.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">1</set>
			<set name="school">Necromancy</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a joint bone</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Cruel Puppetry" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_CRUEL_PUPPETRY">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You attempt to bind a creatures soul to a doll, binding the creature to the doll in a sympathetic link. The target must make a Charisma saving throw. On failure, the creature becomes bound to the doll. On a successful save, the creature is not bound and the spell ends.</p>
			<p class="indent">As part of casting the spell when the creature fails the save, and on subsequent turns using your action until the spell ends, you can perform one of the following actions:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Hold the doll still, causing the creature to be Restrained until start of your next turn.</li>
				<li>Force the doll to move, causing the creature to move 15 feet in a direction of your choice that it can move.</li>
				<li>Smash the doll, causing it take 4d6 bludgeoning damage.</li>
				<li>Rip the doll in half, ending the spell, destroying the doll, and dealing 4d12 necrotic damage.</li>
			</ul>
			<p class="indent">Each time after the first you use an action to manipulate the doll, after the effect takes place, the creature can repeat the Charisma with disadvantage, ending the effect on a successful save.</p>
			<p class="indent">Once a creature has been targeted by this spell, they cannot be targeted again for 24 hours.</p>
			<p class="indent"><b><i>At Higher Levels. </i></b>When cast with a 5th level spell slot or above, the range of the spell becomes unlimited, as long as the target is on the same plane as the caster.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">3</set>
			<set name="school">Necromancy</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">120 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a small humanoid doll worth at least 5 gp and something from the target creature (such as blood, hair, or scales) both of which the spell consumes</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">true</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Decaying Touch" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_DECAYING_TOUCH">
		<supports>Druid, Sorcerer, Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You wreath your hand in necrotic decay that causes anything you touch to wither and die. Make a melee spell attack against the target. On hit, the targets takes 1d6 necrotic damage is starts to flake and decay. The first time they take damage from another source before the start of your next turn, they take an additional 1d6 necrotic damage. Targets immune to diseases are immune to this effect.</p>
			<p class="indent">The both the initial and secondary damage of the spell increases by 1d6 when you reach 5th level (2d6), 11th level (3d6), and 17th level (4d6).</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">0</set>
			<set name="school">Transmutation</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Instantaneous</set>
			<set name="range">Touch</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">powdered remains of a dead animal</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Deglove Creature" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_DEGLOVE_CREATURE">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You point at a creature within range, and attempt to make it's skeleton rip free of it's body. The creature must make a Constitution saving throw. The target takes 7d10 + 7 necrotic damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
			<p class="indent">If this damage kills the target creature, it's flesh sloughs of it's skeleton, collapsing a pile, and the skeleton becomes a Skeleton (Basic Rules, pg. 152), hostile to all living creatures that attacks the closest target.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">5</set>
			<set name="school">Necromancy</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Instantaneous</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a finger bone</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Electrify" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_ELECTRIFY">
		<supports>Occultist, Sorcerer, Wizard</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You channel lightning into your hands. After casting this spell, if you make a successful melee spell attack, unarmed strike or a melee weapon attack with a weapon made of a conductive material (such as metal), the target takes 1d10 lightning damage and must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, the target becomes stunned until the start of their next turn. The spell ends after dealing damage, or at the start of your next turn, whichever occurs first.</p>
			<p class="indent">For the duration of the spell, you can cast the spell <i>shocking grasp</i>.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">1</set>
			<set name="school">Evocation</set>
			<set name="time">1 bonus action</set>
			<set name="duration">1 Round</set>
			<set name="range">Self</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a pair of singed gloves</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Earth Ripple" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_EARTH_RIPPLE">
		<supports>Druid, Occultist, Sorcerer, Wizard</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You cause the earth to deform and ripple, a target creature must make a Dexterity saving throw or suffer one of the following effects (your choice):</p>
			<ul>
				<li>They are pulled into the earth, taking 1d8 bludgeoning damage and having their movement speed dropped to zero until a creature spends an action to dig them free.</li>
				<li>They are slammed in a direction of your choosing, taking 2d8 bludgeoning damage, being moved 5 feet, and knocked prone.</li>
				<li>They are impaled by a spike of earth, taking 4d8 piercing damage.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">2</set>
			<set name="school">Transmutation</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Instantaneous</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">false</set>
			<set name="materialComponent" />
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Form of Familiar" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_FORM_OF_FAMILIAR">
		<supports>Occultist, Wizard</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You assume the form of the familiar that provided the material component to the spell. The transformation lasts for the duration, or until you drop to 0 hit points or die. Your game Statistics are replaced by the Statistics of the chosen creature, though you retain your Alignment and Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores.</p>
			<p class="indent">You assume the Hit Points and Hit Dice of the new form. When you revert to your normal, you return to the number of Hit Points you had before you transformed. If you revert as a result of Dropping to 0 Hit Points, any excess damage carries over to your normal form. As long as the excess damage doesn't reduce your normal form to 0 Hit Points, you aren't knocked Unconscious. You can use an action to revert to your normal form at any time.</p>
			<p class="indent">You are limited in the actions you can perform by the nature of your new form, and you can't speak, cast spells, or take any other action that requires hands or speech. Your gear melds into the new form. You cannot activate, use, wield, or otherwise benefit from any of your equipment.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">2</set>
			<set name="school">Transmutation</set>
			<set name="time">1 minute</set>
			<set name="duration">1 hour</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a piece of fur, feather, or scale from your familiar, which the spell consumes</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Fists of Fire" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_FISTS_OF_FIRE">
		<supports>Druid, Occultist, Sorcerer</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You cause your fists to erupt in flames. For the duration, your fists become a set of simple natural weapons that deal 1d6 fire damage. You are proficient in these weapons, and they have the Light property.</p>
			<p class="indent">For the duration, any flammable object you attempt to hold catches fire. If you end your turn grappling another creature with your hands, it takes 1d4 fire damage.</p>
			<p class="indent">You can end the spell early (no action required).</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">0</set>
			<set name="school">Transmutation</set>
			<set name="time">1 bonus action</set>
			<set name="duration">1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">Self</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">false</set>
			<set name="materialComponent" />
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Freeze" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_FREEZE">
		<supports>Druid, Occultist, Sorcerer</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You instill a deadly chill into your hand. Make a melee spell attack against the target. On hit, the target takes 1d8 cold damage, and the target's movement speed is reduced by 10 feet.</p>
			<p class="indent">The spell's damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">0</set>
			<set name="school">Transmutation</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Instantaneous</set>
			<set name="range">Touch</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">false</set>
			<set name="materialComponent" />
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Ice Weapon" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_ICE_WEAPON">
		<supports>Druid, Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You conjure a weapon formed from magical ice from the air. You have proficiency with this weapon. When you form it and as a bonus action while wielding it, you can morph the weapon into different forms that take on the following properties. If you lose or discard the weapon, you can reform it in your hand as a bonus action.</p>
			<p class="indent"><b><i>Ice Dagger. </i></b>1d4, Finesse, Thrown (30/90).</p>
			<p class="indent"><b><i>Ice Spear. </i></b>1d6, Thrown (30/90).</p>
			<p class="indent"><b><i>Ice Sword. </i></b>1d6, Versatile (1d8).</p>
			<p class="indent"><b><i>Ice Lance. </i></b>1d8, Two-Handed, Reach.</p>
			<p class="indent"><b><i>Ice Hammer. </i></b>1d10, Two-Handed, Heavy.</p>
			<p class="indent">Regardless of it's form, the weapon deals cold damage. You can end the spell early, letting the weapon melt to a harmless splash of water (no action required). You can have up to three ice weapons formed from this spell at a time. After forming a fourth, the first created one melts away. </p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">0</set>
			<set name="school">Transmutation</set>
			<set name="time">1 bonus action</set>
			<set name="duration">1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">Self</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a drop of water that was once snow</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Induce Headache" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_INDUCE_HEADACHE">
		<supports>Bard, Occultist, Wizard</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Targeting a creature with 6 or more intelligence, you inflict an instantaneous headache on them. The target takes 1 psychic damage at the start of their turns, and has disadvantage on Constitution saving throws to maintain Concentration or Intelligence ability checks. </p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">1</set>
			<set name="school">Evocation</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a bad pun written on a scrap of parchment</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Killing Curse" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_KILLING_CURSE">
		<supports>Druid, Occultist, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You curse a target to die. The targets current and maximum hit points is reduced by 3d10 + 10. If this causes a creatures to have zero hit points, the creature dies.</p>
			<p class="indent">For the duration of the spell, the target cannot regain hit points unless from a magical effect cast by a spell slot of higher level than this spell slot this curse was cast with, and any death saving throw they roll is automatically considered a 1.</p>
			<p class="indent">At the start of a creatures turn while they are under the effect of this spell, they make a Charsima saving throw. On failure, their current and maximum hit points is reduced by 1d10 + 10. On a successful save, the spell ends.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">5</set>
			<set name="school">Enchantment</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">something from the target creature (such as blood, hair, or scales) which the spell consumes</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Nauseating Poison" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_NAUSEATING_POISON">
		<supports>Druid, Occultist, Warlock</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You shroud your hand, a weapon you are holding, or a natural weapon in dark ichorous miasma. After casting this spell, if you make a successful melee spell attack, unarmed strike or a melee weapon attack, the target takes an additional 1d8 poison damage and must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, the target becomes poisoned until the end of your next turn.</p>
			<p class="indent">The spell ends after dealing damage, or at the start of your next turn, whichever occurs first.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">1</set>
			<set name="school">Necromancy</set>
			<set name="time">1 bonus action</set>
			<set name="duration">1 round</set>
			<set name="range">Self</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a piece of rotten meat</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Rain of Spiders" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_RAIN_OF_SPIDERS">
		<supports>Druid, Occultist, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</supports>
		<description>
			<p>A vertical column of spiders begins to rain down in 20 foot radius, 40 foot high cylinder, centered on a location you specify. A Swarm of Spiders (Monster Manual, pg 334) descends onto each creature within the cylinder.</p>
			<p class="indent">This swarm is considered to be climbing on the target creature and moves with them, even if they leave the affected area, and takes its turn immediately after that creature's turn. A creature can make use its action to attempt to get them off, making a Strength (Athletics) or Dexterity (Acrobatics) check against the spell save DC of the caster.</p>
			<p class="indent">The swarm will attack the creature it fell on if it can, or move to chase them if it has been knocked off of them. Any spiders that remain when the spell ends disappear.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">3</set>
			<set name="school">Conjuration</set>
			<set name="time">1 bonus action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a spider leg</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Rotting Curse" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_ROTTING_CURSE">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You inflicting a rotting decay on a creature, causing it to to begin to rot. For the duration of the spell, every time the creature takes damage, it takes an additional 1d4 necrotic damage, and the effect of all healing on the creature is reduced by half.</p>
			<p class="indent">The target creature has disadvantage on any Charisma checks for social interaction during the effect of the spell.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">1</set>
			<set name="school">Necromancy</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">something from the target creature (such as blood, hair, or scales) which the spell consumes</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Spiritual Consultation" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_SPIRITUAL_CONSULTATION">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You call forth a spirit that is proficient in a skill from Arcana, Animal Handling, History, Investigation, Medicine, Nature, Perception, Religion, or Survival. The spirit is ethereal and ephemeral and cannot interact with physical objects, but can provide guidance on matters relating to the skill selected when you summon it.</p>
			<p class="indent">You can treat any check you make in the skill as if you have proficiency with it so long as the spirit can communicate with you. Alternatively, if the ability check is an Intelligence or Wisdom check you can have the spirit make the check, and it has a +8 modifier for the skill was summoned for.</p>
			<p class="indent">The spirit will follow you and cannot stray more than 5 feet from you. You can choose to release it early, dismissing it back from whence it came.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">1</set>
			<set name="school">Necromancy</set>
			<set name="time">1 minute</set>
			<set name="duration">10 minutes</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">1 gp worth of incense, which the spell consumes</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Swapping Curse" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_SWAPPING_CURSE">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You cast a curse targeting two individuals. Both targets must make a Charisma saving throw (which they can choose to fail). If both targets fail their saving throws, for the duration of the spell their souls swapped. A soul controls the body it inhabits. It gains any ability score or action the body had (besides legendary actions or legendary resistance), but retains it's own spell casting (if it has the spellcasting, innate or otherwise), and has disadvantage on all attack rolls and strength, dexterity, and constitution saving throws for 1d4 turns after swapping bodies.</p>
			<p class="indent">At the end of a swapped creatures turn, it can choose to repeat the saving throw, ending the effect on a successful save. It its CR (or character level if it has no CR) is higher than the body of the creature it is, it has advantage on the save.</p>
			<p class="indent">If a creature dies while while it's soul is swapped, the souls return to their original bodies. If a soul was in a dying creature that returns to a living body, that creature takes 5d10 necrotic damage.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">5</set>
			<set name="school">Enchantment</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">something from each creature (such as blood, hair, or scales) the spell is targeting, which the spell consumes</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Twisting Eruption" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_TWISTING_ERUPTION">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You target a point and call forth tendrils, twisted vines, and gnarled roots of dark energy that erupt from the ground in a 60 foot radius. All creatures of your choice must make a Dexterity saving throw or be restrained as the shadowy plant tendrils grasp and drain the life from them.</p>
			<p class="indent">At start of a creature's turn, if it is restrained by the spell, it takes 2d10 bludgeoning damage, and 2d10 necrotic damage. Each time a creature takes necrotic damage from this spell, the caster regains 1d4 hit points.</p>
			<p class="indent">A creature restrained by the tendrils can use its action to make a Strength or Dexterity check (its choice) against your spell save DC. On a success, it frees itself. A tendril can be destroyed freeing a creature from its grasp. They have an AC of 10, 20 hit point, and are immune to all damage besides radiant and fire. Spells that deal radiant or fire damage to creatures in an area of effect also effect tendrils in that area.</p>
			<p class="indent">Creatures that end their turn within the radius while not restrained must make a Dexterity saving throw or become restrained by the tendrils.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">7</set>
			<set name="school">Conjuration</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">120 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a handful of dead plants</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Wither" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_WITHER">
		<supports>Occultist</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Dark energy tears the moisture from a body, sapping of life and vitality. The target must make a Constituion saving throw. The target takes 4d10 necrotic damage on a failed save and becomes withered until the start of your next turn, or half as much on a successful one and does not become withered. A withered creature gains vulnerability to fire damage if they are not resistance to fire damage, or loses their resistance to fire if they were resistant to fire.</p>
			<p class="indent"><b><i>At Higher Levels. </i></b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, the damage increases by 1d10 for each slot level above 5th.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">3</set>
			<set name="school">Necromancy</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">1 round</set>
			<set name="range">60 feet</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a pinch of powdered bone and sand</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">false</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Manipulate Fate" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_MANIPULATE_FATE">
		<supports>Occultist, Wizard</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You reach out and grasp the imperceptible threads of fate, subtly manipulating them. Whenever a creature within 60 feet of you makes an attack roll, saving throw, or ability check, you can use your reaction to tweak their fate, altering the value of the roll. You can choose to manipulate fate after the die is rolled, but before the outcome is determined.</p>
			<p class="indent">You can alter the roll of the die to an adjacent number to the number rolled.</p>
			<p class="indent">When you alter a roll, you can choose to cast aside subtlty and yank the thread of fate, and select any value of the d20 as the outcome of the result, but the backlash causes you to take a number d6 equal to the difference in the value selected from the value rolled in necrotic damage. The spell immediately ends after the result is changed in this more drastic way.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">9</set>
			<set name="school">Divination</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">Self</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">true</set>
			<set name="materialComponent">a spool of silk thread</set>
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	
	<!-- https://www.reddit.com/r/UnearthedArcana/comments/bmxuao/spell_orbital_stones_a_gravityearth_spell_for_5e/ -->
	<element name="Orbital Stones" type="Spell" source="r/UA: The Occultist Class" id="ID_REDDITUA_KTTOC_SPELL_ORBITALSTONES">
		<supports>Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You lift three small to medium rocks or similar objects from within 10 feet of you, causing them to defy gravity and slowly circle around you. While all three are in orbit around you, you have total cover against ranged attacks. While two are in orbit, you have three quarters cover, and while only one remains, you have half cover. The spell ends when none of them are orbiting you.</p>
			<p class="indent">As a bonus action while at least one object remains in orbit, you can magically fling it at a target within 60 feet. Make a ranged spell attack. On a hit, the target takes 2d12 bludgeoning damage and is knocked backward 5 feet.</p>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="keywords"/>
			<set name="level">4</set>
			<set name="school">Transmutation</set>
			<set name="time">1 action</set>
			<set name="duration">Concentration, up to 1 minute</set>
			<set name="range">Self</set>
			<set name="hasVerbalComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasSomaticComponent">true</set>
			<set name="hasMaterialComponent">false</set>
			<set name="materialComponent" />
			<set name="isConcentration">true</set>
			<set name="isRitual">false</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	
	
	
	<!-- Append Occultist Spell List -->
	<!-- Cantrips -->
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ACID_SPLASH"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CHILL_TOUCH"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_CREATE_BONFIRE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DANCING_LIGHTS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DRUIDCRAFT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_FROSTBITE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_GUIDANCE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_GUST"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_INFESTATION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_LIGHT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_SCAG_SPELL_LIGHTNING_LURE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_MAGIC_STONE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MENDING"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MESSAGE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MINOR_ILLUSION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_MOLD_EARTH"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_POISON_SPRAY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_PRIMAL_SAVAGERY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_PRODUCE_FLAME"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_SHAPE_WATER"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_THORN_WHIP"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<!-- 1st Level -->
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_ABSORB_ELEMENTS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ANIMAL_FRIENDSHIP"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_BANE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_BEAST_BOND"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_BURNING_HANDS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_CAUSE_FEAR"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_CEREMONY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_COMPREHEND_LANGUAGES"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CURE_WOUNDS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DETECT_MAGIC"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DETECT_POISON_AND_DISEASE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DISGUISE_SELF"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DISSONANT_WHISPERS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ENTANGLE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FEATHER_FALL"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FOG_CLOUD"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_HAIL_OF_THORNS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_ICE_KNIFE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_IDENTIFY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ILLUSORY_SCRIPT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_INFLICT_WOUNDS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_RAY_OF_SICKNESS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SPEAK_WITH_ANIMALS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_TASHAS_HIDEOUS_LAUGHTER"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_UNSEEN_SERVANT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_WITCH_BOLT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<!-- 2nd Level -->
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ALTER_SELF"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ANIMAL_MESSENGER"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_AUGURY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_BARKSKIN"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_BLINDNESS_DEAFNESS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CALM_EMOTIONS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DARKNESS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DARKVISION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DETECT_THOUGHTS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ENHANCE_ABILITY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ENLARGE_REDUCE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_GENTLE_REPOSE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_HEALING_SPIRIT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_HEAT_METAL"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_HOLD_PERSON"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_INVISIBILITY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_LESSER_RESTORATION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_LOCATE_OBJECT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MELFS_ACID_ARROW"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MIRROR_IMAGE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MISTY_STEP"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_PROTECTION_FROM_POISON"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SCORCHING_RAY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SEE_INVISIBILITY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_SHADOW_BLADE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SILENCE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SPIDER_CLIMB"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SPIKE_GROWTH"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SUGGESTION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_WEB"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<!-- 3rd Level -->
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ANIMATE_DEAD"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_BESTOW_CURSE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_BLINK"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_CATNAP"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CLAIRVOYANCE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_COUNTERSPELL"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DISPEL_MAGIC"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FEAR"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FLY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_GASEOUS_FORM"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_HYPNOTIC_PATTERN"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_LIFE_TRANSFERENCE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MAGIC_CIRCLE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_NONDETECTION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_PLANT_GROWTH"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_REMOVE_CURSE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SENDING"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SLEET_STORM"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SLOW"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SPIRIT_GUARDIANS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_VAMPIRIC_TOUCH"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_WALL_OF_WATER"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_WATER_BREATHING"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_WATER_WALK"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_WIND_WALL"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<!-- 4th Level -->
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ARCANE_EYE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_BANISHMENT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_BLIGHT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_CHARM_MONSTER"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_COMPULSION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CONFUSION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CONJURE_MINOR_ELEMENTALS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CONJURE_WOODLAND_BEINGS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CONTROL_WATER"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DIVINATION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_ELEMENTAL_BANE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_EVARDS_BLACK_TENTACLES"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_GIANT_INSECT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_GREATER_INVISIBILITY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_HALLUCINATORY_TERRAIN"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ICE_STORM"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_LEOMUNDS_SECRET_CHEST"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_LOCATE_CREATURE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_POLYMORPH"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_SHADOW_OF_MOIL"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_VITRIOLIC_SPHERE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_WALL_OF_FIRE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_WATERY_SPHERE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<!-- 5th Level -->
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ANIMATE_OBJECTS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_AWAKEN"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CLOUDKILL"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_COMMUNE_WITH_NATURE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CONJURE_ELEMENTAL"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CONTACT_OTHER_PLANE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CONTAGION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_DANSE_MACABRE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DOMINATE_PERSON"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DREAM"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_ENERVATION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_GEAS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_GREATER_RESTORATION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_HOLD_MONSTER"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_INSECT_PLAGUE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MASS_CURE_WOUNDS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MISLEAD"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MODIFY_MEMORY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_NEGATIVE_ENERGY_FLOOD"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_REINCARNATE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SCRYING"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SEEMING"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_SKILL_EMPOWERMENT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_TRANSMUTE_ROCK"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_WALL_OF_STONE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<!-- 6th Level -->
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_BONES_OF_THE_EARTH"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CONJURE_FEY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CONTINGENCY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_CREATE_HOMUNCULUS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_EYEBITE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FIND_THE_PATH"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FLESH_TO_STONE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FORBIDDANCE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_HARM"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_HEAL"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MAGIC_JAR"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MASS_SUGGESTION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_MENTAL_PRISON"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MOVE_EARTH"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_OTILUKES_FREEZING_SPHERE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_PRIMORDIAL_WARD"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_SOUL_CAGE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SUNBEAM"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_TRUE_SEEING"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_WALL_OF_ICE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_WALL_OF_THORNS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_WIND_WALK"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<!-- 7th Level -->
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FINGER_OF_DEATH"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FIRE_STORM"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MIRAGE_ARCANE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_PLANE_SHIFT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_POWER_WORD_PAIN"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_PRISMATIC_SPRAY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_PROJECT_IMAGE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_REGENERATE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_RESURRECTION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SEQUESTER"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_TELEPORT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_WHIRLWIND"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<!-- 8th Level -->
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_ABI_DALZIMS_HORRID_WILTING"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ANIMAL_SHAPES"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ANTIPATHY_SYMPATHY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CLONE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CONTROL_WEATHER"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DEMIPLANE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DOMINATE_MONSTER"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_EARTHQUAKE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FEEBLEMIND"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_INCENDIARY_CLOUD"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_MADDENING_DARKNESS"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MAZE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_MIND_BLANK"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_POWER_WORD_STUN"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_TSUNAMI"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<!-- 9th Level -->
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_ASTRAL_PROJECTION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FORESIGHT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_IMPRISONMENT"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_INVULNERABILITY"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_POWER_WORD_HEAL"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_POWER_WORD_KILL"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_XGTE_SPELL_PSYCHIC_SCREAM"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_TRUE_POLYMORPH"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_TRUE_RESURRECTION"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SHAPECHANGE"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	<append id="ID_PHB_SPELL_WEIRD"><supports>Occultist</supports></append>
	
	
</elements>